Rajkamal Prasad

- https://rajkamalpr.github.io/rajkamalprasad/

Summary

I am a Frontend Developer with 2.2 years of expertise in creating UI, integrating APIs, and ensuring UI functionality using React JS, React Native, Redux, CSS, and design frameworks. Demonstrated exceptional time-management skills by consistently delivering projects within strict deadlines. Proven leadership abilities in coordinating and leading development teams to successfully accomplish project goals.

Skill:

JavaScript | React JS | React Native | Typescript | Ant Design | Redux | Bootstrap | Git | Jest | HTML | CSS.

Experience

React Native | Wezbo

Nov 2023 - Feb 2024

- Present Tech stack: JavaScript, Redux, Typescript and react native -Working as react native developer, all resources are provided like icons and images and Figma design etc, I only have to design mobile app and report it back to my reporting manager.

Frontend Developer | WeblineIndia

May 2022 - Mar 2023

Projects: Amplify-lite, botworx-ui, etc.

Tech stack: React, Redux, JavaScript, TypeScript and Jest.

- -Collaborated with cross-functional team to successfully accomplish assigned tasks and maintain efficient workflow. proactively reported progress and sought guidance from team leader to ensure timely updates were provided to clients.
- -Actively participated in team meetings, delivering comprehensive updates and discussing ongoing assignments, while effectively addressing any challenges faced with the support of the team.

Software Developer | Exist

Apr 2021 - Apr 2022

Projects: Food delivery app, CRM/CMS for affiliated marketing web application, Fight Right.

Tech stack: React, Redux, JavaScript, Node, React Native.

-Implemented software solutions for various projects including "food delivery", "CRM/CMS for Affiliated marketing", and "Fight Right". Contributed to the planning, design, coding, debugging, testing, and maintenance of software applications.

Education

M.C.A | ASM IMCOST, Thane, Mumbai University

Jul 2017 - May 2020

Information Technology

B.Sc | G.V.M, Thane, Mumbai University

Jul 2014 - May 2017

Information Technology